<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LearnHangul</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- Error messages -->
    <string name="error_load_syllables">Failed to load file for syllables.</string>
    <string name="error_load_vowels_progress">Failed to load progress status for vowels.</string>
    <string name="error_load_vowels_default">Failed to load default file for vowels.</string>
    <string name="error_load_consonants_progress">Failed to load progress status for consonants.</string>
    <string name="error_load_consonants_default">Failed to load default file for consonants.</string>
    <string name="error_save_vowels_progress">Failed to save progress status for vowels.</string>
    <string name="error_save_consonants_progress">Failed to save progress status for consonants.</string>

    <!-- Toolbar titles -->
    <string name="toolbar_title_study">Study</string>
    <string name="toolbar_title_vowels">Vowels</string>
    <string name="toolbar_title_consonants">Consonants</string>
    <string name="toolbat_title_about_hangul">About Hangul</string>
    <string name="toolbar_title_review">Review</string>
    <string name="toolbar_title_from_character">Choose the transcription</string>
    <string name="toolbar_title_from_transcription">Choose the character</string>
    <string name="toolbar_title_from_syllable_character">Choose the transcription</string>
    <string name="toolbar_title_from_syllable_transcription">Choose the syllable</string>

    <!-- Button texts -->
    <string name="button_main_study">Study</string>
    <string name="button_main_review">Review</string>
    <string name="button_study_vowels">Vowels</string>
    <string name="button_study_consonants">Consonants</string>
    <string name="button_study_about_hangul">How Hangul works</string>
    <string name="button_review_from_character">Find transcription</string>
    <string name="button_review_from_transcription">Find character</string>
    <string name="button_review_syllable_from_character">Find transcription of syllable</string>
    <string name="button_review_syllable_from_transcription">Find syllable</string>

    <!-- Popup window when pressing back in a quiz -->
    <string name="popup_exit_quiz_text">Are you sure you want to exit the quiz?</string>
    <string name="popup_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="popup_no">Cancel</string>

    <!-- Popup window when trying to start a quiz without enough characters selected -->
    <string name="popup_not_quiz_text">You need to select at least 2 characters to start doing quizzes</string>
    <string name="popup_not_quiz_understood">Understood</string>

    <!-- Information about the ListView elements in the character study section -->
    <string name="character_column">Character</string>
    <string name="transcription_column">Transcription</string>

    <!-- Information about correctness of an answer in the quizzes -->
    <string name="answer_correct_pre">Correct.&#160;</string>
    <string name="answer_incorrect_pre">Incorrect.&#160;</string>
    <string name="answer_mid">&#160;matches with&#160;</string>

    <!-- Text in the About Hangul activity -->
    <string name="about_hangul">
        \t\tThe Korean alphabet, known as <b>Hangul</b> or <b>Hangeul</b> (한글) in South Korea,
        has been in use, to a greater or lesser extent, since its creation in the 15th century.
        Currently, both South and North Korea favor its use over <b>Hanja</b> (한자 / 漢字)
        or Chinese characters.\n\n

        \t\tIt is composed of 10 <b>vowels</b> and 14 <b>consonants</b> that can be combined to form
        <b>syllables</b>. These syllables must begin with a consonant, after which we must place a
        vowel. Syllables can end either with a vowel or with a consonant.\n\n

        \t\t<b>Vowels.</b> We can distinguish two main types: vertical ones (ㅏ or ㅓ) and horizontal
        ones (ㅗ or ㅜ). The difference between them lies in where the initial consonant of the
        syllable will be placed; for the vertical ones, it will be on its left, and for the
        horizontal ones, it will be above them. In addition, we have a set of special vowels that
        contain the sound <i>y</i> (ㅑ or ㅛ) and behave just like we have learned. Finally, we can
        form diphthongs, like ㅐ or ㅟ; you can observe that the former is just like before, and the
        latter has a little gap in its upper left corner for you to place a consonant. As every one
        of them behaves exactly like a vowel in a syllable, we have grouped them together for
        simplicity.\n\n

        \t\t<b>Consonants.</b> Consonants are the characters that begin and optionally end a
        syllable. A special case here is ㅇ, which acts as a null consonant when our syllable starts
        with a vowel, but has its own sound when we place it at the end of the syllable. This
        pattern of having different sounds depending on their location inside the syllable is not
        unique to ㅇ: ㄷ, ㅅ, ㅆ, ㅈ, ㅊ and ㅎ all change their transcription to <i>t</i> when placed
        at the end; ㄱ and ㄲ change to <i>k</i>; ㅂ changes to <i>p</i>.\n\n

        \t\t<b>Syllables.</b> These are the basic units used to form words. Syllables are compound
        character blocks that contain one or more consonants and exactly one vowel (including
        diphthongs and the vowels with <i>y</i> sounds). To build them, we follow a similar approach
        to that used when grouping a single vowel with a consonant: the first letters tend to be
        placed at the top and/or on the left, while the final letters are usually at the bottom,
        with any medial ones being just between them in the remaining gap.\n\n

        \t\t<b>Examples.</b>\n
        \t\t-<b>Vowels:</b> ㅏ (<i>a</i>) and ᅩ (<i>o</i>), associated with the syllables 아 and 오.\n
        \t\t-<b>Syllables:</b>\n
        \t\t\t수 (<i>su</i>): ㅅ (<i>s</i>) + ㅜ (<i>u</i>)\n
        \t\t\t쟁 (<i>jaeng</i>): ㅈ (<i>j</i>) + ㅐ (<i>ae</i>) + ㅇ (<i>ng</i>)\n
        \t\t\t넣 (<i>neot</i>): ㄴ (<i>n</i>) + ㅓ (<i>eo</i>) + ㅎ (<i>t</i> at the end of a syllable)\n
        \t\t\t한 (<i>han</i>): ㅎ (<i>h</i>) + ㅏ (<i>a</i>) + ㄴ (<i>n</i>)\n
        \t\t\t글 (<i>geul</i>): ㄱ (<i>g</i>) + ㅡ (<i>eu</i>) + ㄹ (<i>l</i>).\n\n

        \t\t<b>Note on pronunciation.</b> The transcriptions provided here are just a way to write
        the characters using the Latin alphabet, and thus they do not stand for pronunciations.
        Inclusion of audio files to help in this matter is not currently planned, but we encourage
        learners to expose themselves to native material as soon as possible.

    </string>

</resources>
